{"problem": "Find the number of rectangles that can be formed inside a fixed regular dodecagon (12-gon) where each side of the rectangle lies on either a side or a diagonal of the dodecagon. Note that it is possible for a rectangle to be contained within another rectangle, and that the rectangles may not extend beyond the boundaries of the 12-gon.", "answer": 315}
{"problem": "Find the number of squares that can be formed inside a fixed regular dodecagon (12-gon) where each side of the square lies on either a side or a diagonal of the dodecagon. Note that it is possible for a square to be contained within another square, and that the squares may not extend beyond the boundaries of the 12-gon.", "answer": 45}
{"problem": "Find the number of rectangles that can be formed inside a fixed regular 19-gon where each side of the rectangle lies on either a side or a diagonal of the 19-gon. Note that it is possible for a rectangle to be contained within another rectangle, and that the rectangles may not extend beyond the boundaries of the 19-gon.", "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Find the number of squares that can be formed inside a fixed regular hexagon where each side of the square lies on either a side or a diagonal of the hexagon. Note that it is possible for a square to be contained within another square, and that the squares may not extend beyond the boundaries of the hexagon.", "answer": 0}
{"problem": "Find the number of rectangles that can be formed inside a fixed regular hexagon where each side of the rectangle lies on either a side or a diagonal of the hexagon. Note that it is possible for a rectangle to be contained within another rectangle, and that the rectangles may not extend beyond the boundaries of the hexagon.", "answer": 9}
{"problem": "Find the number of rectangles that can be formed inside a fixed regular octagon where each side of the rectangle lies on either a side or a diagonal of the octagon. Note that it is possible for a rectangle to be contained within another rectangle, and that the rectangles may not extend beyond the boundaries of the octagon.", "answer": 40}
{"problem": "Find the number of squares that can be formed inside a fixed regular octagon where each side of the square lies on either a side or a diagonal of the octagon. Note that it is possible for a square to be contained within another square, and that the squares may not extend beyond the boundaries of the octagon.", "answer": 20}
{"problem": "Find the number of rectangles that can be formed inside a fixed regular 10-gon where each side of the rectangle lies on either a side or a diagonal of the 10-gon. Note that it is possible for a rectangle to be contained within another rectangle, and that the rectangles may not extend beyond the boundaries of the 10-gon.", "answer": 125}
{"problem": "A regular hexagon is drawn, and all of the diagonals between vertices two-apart are drawn (i.e, none of the longest diagonals are drawn). Find the number of triangles that can be formed inside the hexagon, where each side of the triangle lies on a side or one of the diagonals drawn. Note that some triangles may be contained within other triangles.", "answer": 32}
{"problem": "A regular hexagon is drawn, and all of the diagonals between vertices two-apart are drawn (i.e, none of the longest diagonals are drawn). Find the number of non-equilateral isoceles triangles that can be formed inside the hexagon, where each side of the triangle lies on a side or one of the diagonals drawn. Note that some triangles may be contained within other triangles.", "answer": 12}
{"problem": "A regular hexagon is drawn, and all of the diagonals between vertices three-apart are drawn (i.e, the longest diagonals are drawn). Find the number of convex polygons that can be formed inside the hexagon, where each side of the polygon lies on a side or one of the diagonals drawn, not including the hexagon itself. Note that some polygons may be contained within other polygons.", "answer": 18}
{"problem": "A regular hexagon is drawn, and all of the diagonals between vertices three-apart are drawn (i.e, the longest diagonals are drawn). Find the number of triangles that can be formed inside the hexagon, where each side of the polygon lies on a side or one of the diagonals drawn, not including the hexagon itself. Note that some polygons may be contained within other polygons.", "answer": 18}
{"problem": "Find the number of triangles that can be formed inside a fixed regular pentagon where each side of the triangle lies on either a side or a diagonal of the pentagon. Note that it is possible for a triangle to be contained within another triangle, and that the triangles may not extend beyond the boundaries of the pentagon.", "answer": 35}
{"problem": "Find the number of equilateral triangles that can be formed inside a fixed regular hexagon where each side of the triangle lies on either a side or a diagonal of the hexagon. Note that it is possible for a triangle to be contained within another triangle, and that the triangles may not extend beyond the boundaries of the hexagon.", "answer": 8}
{"problem": "Find the number of non-equilateral isoceles triangles that can be formed inside a fixed regular hexagon where each side of the triangle lies on either a side or a diagonal of the hexagon. Note that it is possible for a triangle to be contained within another triangle, and that the triangles may not extend beyond the boundaries of the hexagon.", "answer": 18}
{"problem": "A regular hexagon is drawn, and all of its diagonals are drawn. Find the number of regular hexagons that can be formed, where each side of the formed hexagons lies on an edge of the original hexagon, or one of the drawn diagonals. Do not include the original hexagon.", "answer": 1}
{"problem": "A square is drawn, and its diagonals are drawn. Find the number of triangles that can be formed, where each side of the triangle lies on a side of the square, or one of the drawn diagonals. Note that it is possible for a triangle to be contained within another triangle", "answer": 8}
{"problem": "A square is drawn, and its midpoints are marked. Lines are drawn connecting each pair of midpoints. Find the number of squares that can be formed, where each side of the square lies on a side of the original square, or one of the lines drawn. Note that it is possible for a square to be contained within another square", "answer": 6}
{"problem": "A square is drawn, and its midpoints are marked. Lines are drawn connecting each pair of midpoints. Find the number of triangles that can be formed, where each side of the triangle lies on a side of the original square, or one of the lines drawn. Note that it is possible for a triangle to be contained within another triangle", "answer": 12}
{"problem": "A square is drawn, and its midpoints are marked. Lines are drawn connecting each pair of opposing midpoints. Find the number of squares that can be formed, where each side of the square lies on a side of the original square, or one of the lines drawn. Note that it is possible for a square to be contained within another square", "answer": 5}
{"problem": "A square is drawn, and its midpoints are marked. Lines are drawn connecting each pair of opposing midpoints. Find the number of rectangles that can be formed, where each side of the rectangle lies on a side of the original square, or one of the lines drawn. Note that it is possible for a rectangle to be contained within another rectangle", "answer": 9}
